Changhuan.
We're here.
"The Last Oath"
(Episode 13: Post-Outbreak
Infection Research)
Sleep well last night?
Yeah.
Not again.
It's torn open.
I'm talking about your wound.
What were you thinking?
I'm fine.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
My fever's gone too.
Let's get down to business.
He Yao drove the car away.
What do we do now?
If we follow the highway,
we should be able to find a working car.
Let's go.
Walk properly.
What's wrong? Did your
wound tear open again?
How childish can you be?
Very childish.
So what?
Big baby.
This place...
is actually pretty well-preserved.
Yeah.
Let's take a break.
For a split second just now,
I thought we were back
before the apocalypse.
It felt like...
this was just a normal date.
Did you come to places like this often?
Do you mean...
on dates,
or to watch performances?
This is my first date.
I rarely went to performances before, either.
Have you ever experienced
anything like this?
Let's eat first.
You're so lazy.
This...
It's fine.
It's far enough away.
I didn't expect zombies to retain
the skills they had when they were alive.
Tell me,
do you think zombies might still have
a little bit of human consciousness left?
Is it possible that one day,
zombies could turn back into humans?
It's just muscle memory.
Zombies are zombies.
They can't turn back.
Where are we?
He Yao,
what exactly are you trying to do?
Stop feeding me this useless stuff.
There's no going back.
I know that myself.
I have a plan.
Just give me some time.
The equipment here is old,
but it works perfectly...
He Yao, you're always like this.
Always acting like you have
everything under control.
But when have you ever cared
about what others think?
Do you know
that the way you are right now
is exactly like when you
suddenly barged into my life?
Leave.
Get out of here.
I don't want to see you.
Yao,
this will be your home from now on.
Make yourself at home.
Changhuan is back.
Come here.
This is your older brother, He Yao.
You've met before.
Do you remember?
He'll be living with us from now on.
Yeah, I know.
I'm going to my room.
Your bed...
Changhuan is a bit shy around strangers.
Mom.
Changhuan, you're back.
Here, give it to me.
What do you want to eat?
Mom will make it for you.
Today I want to eat...
Yao,
what happened to you?
How did you cut your head?
Come sit down.
Let me disinfect it for you.
It's fine, Auntie.
I accidentally fell.
Your head is bleeding.
How did this happen?
How could you be so careless?
It's fine, Auntie.
Let me clean it a bit more.
I'll be gentle.
You're too careless. Let's change it.
Come on, Dad is working overtime.
Let's eat first.
Come on, eat up.
Here.
Today,
Mr. Wang called specifically to say
that for this midterm exam,
the top two students in the
grade are both in our family.
I'm so happy.
Auntie, Changhuan is the amazing one.
For that big math problem this time,
his solution was incredibly unique.
Even the teacher didn't think of it.
Really?
You are both my pride and joy.
Auntie,
Changhuan and I will definitely
keep up the good work.
I'm full.
This time,
I didn't do well.
Changhuan! Changhuan!
What's with that kid...
Do you want some water?
Drinking too much water at night
is bad for your kidneys.
Still studying this late?
It's for the Math Olympiad, right?
For this problem, it...
I'll study on my own.
Ever since we were kids,
I've tried my hardest,
but it seems I'm always
one step behind you.
He Yao,
in your eyes,
do I always need you to take care of me?
You're my younger brother.
Of course I have to take care of you.
I'm not your brother.
I'm Shen Changhuan.
I don't care what you think.
You...
Since we're tied together now,
this path,
we have to walk it together.
You don't have the option to ditch me.
You never did.
The infection in your
wound is getting worse.
We need to find antibiotics, fast.
Let's rest for a bit.
Wait here and don't move.
I'll check if there's water in the well.
Come back!
Why did you come over?
I wanted to keep an eye on you.
I told you not to move.
Don't move.
Hey, friends.
Where are you folks from?